I eat an entire pint of ice cream every
single night and still maintain a
caloric deficit. Here are some of the
recipes I made this week to stay fit and
hit my protein goal. Started it off with
a Fruity Pebbles ice cream, a little bit
of Red 40, a little bit of crunch. You
can't beat it. Then I recreated my
all-time favorite Ben & Jerry's flavor
fish food. This was a chocolate base
with fudge chunks, marshmallow swirl,
and a caramel drizzle. And after 83 days
of commenting, I finally took this
viewer's request and made oatmeal cream
pie. This was a vanilla cinnamon base
with oatmeal cream pies mixed in and a
marshmallow swirl. And I made one of my
most underrated recipes, the soda float.
This was a Dr. Pepper version, but it's
literally just a protein shake plus your
favorite diet soda. Comes out delicious
every single time. Now, these next three
aren't out on my channel yet, but they
will be in the next week or two. So,
drop me a follow to see them when they
come out. This first one is a matcha
base with Oreos mixed in. Pretty simple,
but it is absolutely ridiculously good.
Then, this next one is a Ben & Jerry's
Netflix and chilled recreation. It is a
peanut butter base topped with brownie
pieces and pretzels. This flavor is just
the definition of sweet and salty. And I
ended off the week by recreating my
first BaskinRobins flavor. This was
Jamoka almond fudge, which is a coffee
base with a chocolate fudge swirl and
roasted almonds.